

Contact

Phone

+962-77-2456-708

Email

alnsourasmaa@gmail.com

Linked In

https://www.linkedin.com/in/asmaa-alnsour/

Github

github.com/AsmaaAlnsour

Address

Amman, Jordan

Technical Skills

- PHP
- JavaScript
- React
- Laravel
- WordPress
- HTML
- CSS
- UI/UX
- Bootstrap
- MySQL
- Mockup
- Wireframes
- Database Design
- SQL
- Trello
- Git

ASMA'A Al-Nsour

Full-Stack Web Developer

Full Stack Developer, transitioning from working as a Civil Engineer to the world of technology. My unique experience and my strong background in Engineering has allowed me to transition into software development with ease, this fast paced and ever-changing environment.

Experience

O Jun 2022 - Present

Coding Academy by Orange, Jordan.

Full-Stack Web Developer Trainee

- Write optimal front-end and back-end code using React, Laravel, PHP, JavaScript, CSS, HTML and etc.
- \cdot Create quality UI mockups, storyboards, and prototypes and working alongside UX designers for web design features.
- · Design relational data models.
- · Familiarity with modern web development tools and patterns, e.g. npm.
- \cdot Extensive experience building web applications with technologies such as React and Node.is.
- · Write clean, consistent and well-documented code.
- · Design, implement, test, and maintain web applications using a variety of web technologies and libraries.

Feb 2020 - Jun 2022

Mindset - Middle East and Africa, Amman, Jordan

Operation Support Specialist

• Ensures that the business runs smoothly, effectively, and professionally. And linking between operation department and the researchers in the field, by taking notes and results of studies from them and organizing it in the Excel sheet.

Mar 2019 - Jan 2020

Nielsen, Amman Jordan.

Research Officer

 \cdot An office researcher who was taking randomly calls to fill surveys in different studies.

Mar 2018 - Mar 2019

Ministry of Public Works and Housing, Amman Jordan.

Quantity Calculation Engineer Trainee

· Collect information on work done quantities, material on site. Review and calculate monthly statements submitted by contractors. Regular update of overall project cost estimates by completion. Estimate required quantities and costs of variations for civil works contracts.

Sep 2017 - Jan 2018

Royal Scientific Society, Amman Jordan

Civil Engineer Trainee

·Training on structural design, plan and oversee the construction of new buildings.

Technical Skills

- Microsoft Visual Studio Code
- problem-solving
- Data Analysis
- Microsoft office platform

Personal Skills

- Team Leadership
- Problem Solving
- Project Planning
- Research
- Training
- Presentation skills
- Time Management
- Communication
- Teamwork

Language

English

Arabic

Education

P 2021

Coding Academy by Orange, Al Balqa', Jordan.

Full-stack Web Developer Trainee

- · 28-weeks Bootcamp of software development that includes programming skills like CSS, HTML, JavaScript, PHP, SQL and etc.. This is a full-time, immersive class that over 28-weeks will cover a career-focused curriculum that provides students with the foundation of being a Jr. full-stack software developer.
- · Projects: Creating a wireframe and mockup for hotel website, building portfolio, building in-house employee evaluation website using JavaScript, WordPress E-Commerce website, building E-Commerce Website (PHP& MySQL), building pharmacy management system in Laravel and etc..

2018

Al-Balqa' Applied university, Al-Balqa', Jordan

B.Sc. in Civil Engineering

 \cdot Graduation Project title: "Structural analysis and design of a residential and entertainment building ".

TRAINING AND MEMBERSHIPS

2019

E-Marketing and Tourism Certificate

·NATA company, Jordan

2018

Jordan Engineers Association

·NATA company, Jordan

2017

Quantity Surveying Calculations Training Course

· Jordan Engineers Association, Jordan

COMMUNITY SERVICE

- O Leaded the team of "Ya'mor" and participate in their activities
- Volunteering Reading Club
- O Volunteering at Jordan Red Crescent